<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- Plague Turret - A long-ranged turret that can pelt targets from a distance. Low DPS. -->

  <MP_Turret_PlagueTurret.label>plague sniper turret</MP_Turret_PlagueTurret.label>
  <MP_Turret_PlagueTurret.description>A portable, automatic, long-ranged turret, designed to fire Mechanite Plague inflicitng darts. It lacks raw damage potential, but the plague application makes it a good supporting defense. Requires fresh doses of mechanites to replenish its ammo. May explode when damaged. Its dumb AI brain can't be directly controlled, so beware of friendly fire.</MP_Turret_PlagueTurret.description>

  <MP_Bullet_MechaniteDartTurret.label>mechanite dart</MP_Bullet_MechaniteDartTurret.label>

  <MP_Gun_PlagueTurret.label>plague sniper gun</MP_Gun_PlagueTurret.label>
  <MP_Gun_PlagueTurret.description>A simple automatic gun made to be mounted on a turret. Fires plague-inducing darts.</MP_Gun_PlagueTurret.description>


  <!-- Plague Shredder - A turret that's supremely accurate, durable, and powerful. Incredibly ammo-hungry and short-ranged. High DPS. -->

  <MP_Turret_PlagueShredder.label>plague shredder turret</MP_Turret_PlagueShredder.label>
  <MP_Turret_PlagueShredder.description>A portable, automatic turret that fires a barrage of Mechanite Plague inducing shrapnel. While incredibly powerful, it has a short range and needs large amounts of Mechanite Canisters to replenish its ammo. Won't explode when damaged, making it ideal for indoor defense. Its dumb AI brain can't be directly controlled, so beware of friendly fire.</MP_Turret_PlagueShredder.description>

  <MP_Bullet_MechaniteFragTurret.label>mechanite shard</MP_Bullet_MechaniteFragTurret.label>

  <MP_Gun_PlagueShredder.label>plague shredder gun</MP_Gun_PlagueShredder.label>
  <MP_Gun_PlagueShredder.description>A short-ranged, destructive, automatic gun made to be mounted on a turret. Fires storms of shrapnel.</MP_Gun_PlagueShredder.description>


  <!-- Plague Landmine -->

  <MP_TrapIED_PlagueSharpnel.label>IED plague shrapnel trap</MP_TrapIED_PlagueSharpnel.label>
  <MP_TrapIED_PlagueSharpnel.description>A high explosive shell, combined with shrapel that inflicts the Mechanite Plague. Detonates in a wide area on touch or bullet impact, but deals very little damage. Since it is hidden in the surrounding terrain, it cannot be placed adjacent to other traps. Animals can sense these when calm.</MP_TrapIED_PlagueSharpnel.description>


  <!-- Punji Sticks -->

  <MP_TrapPunjiSticks.label>punji sticks</MP_TrapPunjiSticks.label>
  <MP_TrapPunjiSticks.description>A series of spikes hidden in the ground. Unfortunate victims will find their skin pierced by sharp spikes, inflicting high damage. In addition, the spikes are coated with poison containing the Mechanite Plague, causing the trap to infect them. This cannot be placed adjacent to other traps. Animals can sense these when calm.</MP_TrapPunjiSticks.description>


  <!-- Caltrops - VFE:Security only -->

  <MP_TrapCaltrops.label>caltrops</MP_TrapCaltrops.label>
  <MP_TrapCaltrops.description>A loose pile of poisoned four-pointed spikes, scattered across the ground. While they deal minimal damage, the sheer amount of caltrops scattered across the ground ensures that the trap will last long enough for multiple intruders to tread over them, the poison infecting them all with the Mechanite Plague. Animals can sense these when calm.</MP_TrapCaltrops.description>


</LanguageData>