<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- Guardian Mechanites - Blocks Mechanite Plague -->

  <MP_GuardianMechanites.label>guardian mechanites</MP_GuardianMechanites.label>
  <MP_GuardianMechanites.description>A specialized injector loaded with altered mechanites. With the addition of medical components, this batch of the plague ends up destroying newly-introduced instances of the Mechanite Plague within the body. It's long lasting, so one dose will protect the user for a quadrum. Also slightly boosts blood filtration.</MP_GuardianMechanites.description>
  <MP_GuardianMechanites.ingestible.ingestCommandString>Inject {0}</MP_GuardianMechanites.ingestible.ingestCommandString>
  <MP_GuardianMechanites.ingestible.ingestReportString>Injecting {0}.</MP_GuardianMechanites.ingestible.ingestReportString>


  <!-- Stimulant Mechanites - Temporary, incredibly powerful speed boost! Followed by a crash. -->

  <MP_StimulantMechanites.label>stimulant mechanites</MP_StimulantMechanites.label>
  <MP_StimulantMechanites.description>A specialized injector loaded with altered mechanites. The introduction of psychite into the mechanite batch causes them to overcharge the user's nervous system, increasing the user's consciousness and movement speed for a short time. While there is no risk of addiction, there is a lengthy crash that leaves the user feeling drained and disoriented for far longer than the high.</MP_StimulantMechanites.description>
  <MP_StimulantMechanites.ingestible.ingestCommandString>Inject {0}</MP_StimulantMechanites.ingestible.ingestCommandString>
  <MP_StimulantMechanites.ingestible.ingestReportString>Injecting {0}.</MP_StimulantMechanites.ingestible.ingestReportString>


  <!-- Reanimator Mechanites - Revives after death -->

  <MP_ReanimatorMechanites.label>reanimator mechanites</MP_ReanimatorMechanites.label>
  <MP_ReanimatorMechanites.description>A specialized injector loaded with altered mechanites. The power of glitterworld medicine and advanced programming allows this batch of mechanites to preserve the host's genetic blueprint at the moment before their death. Then, after some delay, the user will be revived. It's long lasting, so one dose will protect the user from an untimely demise for ten days.</MP_ReanimatorMechanites.description>
  <MP_ReanimatorMechanites.ingestible.ingestCommandString>Inject {0}</MP_ReanimatorMechanites.ingestible.ingestCommandString>
  <MP_ReanimatorMechanites.ingestible.ingestReportString>Injecting {0}.</MP_ReanimatorMechanites.ingestible.ingestReportString>


</LanguageData>